<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Hax</title><link>https://hax.tristen.wtf/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Hax</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hax.tristen.wtf/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hax.init()</title><link>https://hax.tristen.wtf/posts/hello/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hax.tristen.wtf/posts/hello/</guid><description>Welcome! My name is Tristen, and this is the inagural post of Hax, a simple blog about whatever it is I am working on at the moment.
I am currently (as of writing) a senior at Stanford University studying Computer Science focusing on Systems and Security. I primarily focus on digital privacy, OS Development, modern programming language paradigms, and self-hosting as many things as I can.
I created this because as my knowledge of Computer Science and Software Engineering grows, and I have begun to take on more and more side projects, it has become really hard to keep up with everything.</description><content>&lt;p>Welcome! My name is Tristen, and
this is the inagural post of Hax, a simple blog about whatever it is I am
working on at the moment.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am currently (as of writing) a senior at Stanford University studying Computer
Science focusing on Systems and Security. I primarily focus on digital privacy,
OS Development, modern programming language paradigms, and self-hosting as many
things as I can.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I created this because as my knowledge of Computer Science and Software
Engineering grows, and I have begun to take on more and more side projects, it
has become really hard to keep up with everything. So, I figured why not write
about it? It gives me something to look back on should I ever forget how or why
I did something.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>However, I could have just hosted some wiki pages or doc directories for my
projects and called it a day, but I think there is value in free and open
information. There are a ton of resources for learning CS, and software
development, but I have found it more difficult to source those resources for
more advanced topics like OS development, Hypervisors and Virtualization,
embedded systems outside of C, etc. Therefore, I hope a lovely side-effect of
this blog is that it can aggregate not only some resources for learning for whom
ever should stumble upon it, but also to frame the information you get
from these resources in a fashion that may be more accessible to some.
Sometimes, the thing holding you back from understanding something is just the
way it is being presented.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I also like to work on things that tend to not have straight-forward guides or
tutorials written, so I hope that writing blog posts for them will open up the
information for others to build on however they choose.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My hope to is be able to publish something at least bi-weekly, but as I am still
in school, this may need some room for flexibility.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anyways, If you have any questions, feel free to visit my personal site by
clicking the &amp;lsquo;About&amp;rsquo; navigation button. There you will be able to get my contact
information.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Tristen&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></content></item></channel></rss>